import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const katakanaDakuten: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ga\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヂ",
      "ガ",
      "ヅ",
      "ベ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ガ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ガ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ga",
      "pi",
      "be",
      "pu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ga"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"gi\"?",
    "options": [
      "デ",
      "ビ",
      "ギ",
      "ゴ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ギ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ギ\"?",
    "options": [
      "be",
      "zu",
      "gi",
      "pu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"gu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギ",
      "グ",
      "デ",
      "バ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "グ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"グ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ba",
      "bi",
      "gu",
      "zo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ge\"?",
    "options": [
      "ジ",
      "ザ",
      "ギ",
      "ゲ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ゲ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ゲ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ji",
      "zo",
      "ge",
      "zu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"go\"?",
    "options": [
      "ビ",
      "ブ",
      "ジ",
      "ゴ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ゴ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ゴ\"?",
    "options": [
      "do",
      "ji",
      "go",
      "bu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "go"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"za\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギ",
      "ポ",
      "ズ",
      "ザ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ザ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ザ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ji",
      "za",
      "ze",
      "go"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "za"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ji\"?",
    "options": [
      "バ",
      "ズ",
      "ボ",
      "ジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ジ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ジ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ji",
      "do",
      "pi",
      "zo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ji"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"zu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ズ",
      "パ",
      "デ",
      "ダ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ズ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ズ\"?",
    "options": [
      "gi",
      "gu",
      "be",
      "zu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ze\"?",
    "options": [
      "ゼ",
      "ビ",
      "ズ",
      "グ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ゼ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ゼ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ze",
      "bo",
      "pu",
      "ge"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ze"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"zo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ピ",
      "ザ",
      "ゾ",
      "グ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ゾ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ゾ\"?",
    "options": [
      "zu",
      "ba",
      "zo",
      "do"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"da\"?",
    "options": [
      "ゾ",
      "ボ",
      "ヂ",
      "ダ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ダ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ダ\"?",
    "options": [
      "gu",
      "bu",
      "da",
      "pa"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ji\"?",
    "options": [
      "ザ",
      "ヂ",
      "ギ",
      "プ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヂ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヂ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ji",
      "ze",
      "zu",
      "de"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ji"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"zu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ペ",
      "パ",
      "ヅ",
      "ジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヅ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ji",
      "ge",
      "bu",
      "zu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"de\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギ",
      "デ",
      "ビ",
      "ジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "デ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"デ\"?",
    "options": [
      "zu",
      "de",
      "ji",
      "pu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "de"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"do\"?",
    "options": [
      "ボ",
      "ド",
      "ダ",
      "デ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ド"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ド\"?",
    "options": [
      "bu",
      "do",
      "ji",
      "za"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "do"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ba\"?",
    "options": [
      "ダ",
      "パ",
      "ズ",
      "バ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "バ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"バ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ba",
      "bo",
      "ji",
      "zu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ba"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"bi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ザ",
      "パ",
      "ビ",
      "デ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ビ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ビ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ba",
      "gi",
      "de",
      "bi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"bu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ビ",
      "ギ",
      "ブ",
      "ガ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ブ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ブ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bu",
      "bo",
      "de",
      "po"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"be\"?",
    "options": [
      "ゼ",
      "ピ",
      "ベ",
      "ジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ベ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ベ\"?",
    "options": [
      "be",
      "da",
      "do",
      "pu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "be"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"bo\"?",
    "options": [
      "グ",
      "ボ",
      "ポ",
      "パ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ボ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ボ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bu",
      "ba",
      "pi",
      "bo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pa\"?",
    "options": [
      "ポ",
      "ズ",
      "パ",
      "ギ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "パ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"パ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bo",
      "ze",
      "do",
      "pa"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ピ",
      "ド",
      "ポ",
      "ベ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ピ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ピ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bi",
      "ji",
      "gi",
      "pi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ビ",
      "バ",
      "ペ",
      "プ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "プ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"プ\"?",
    "options": [
      "pu",
      "pa",
      "ga",
      "ge"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pe\"?",
    "options": [
      "ゲ",
      "プ",
      "ペ",
      "ボ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ペ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ペ\"?",
    "options": [
      "pe",
      "bi",
      "zu",
      "ba"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pe"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"po\"?",
    "options": [
      "ゴ",
      "バ",
      "ポ",
      "ゲ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ポ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ポ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ge",
      "go",
      "po",
      "gi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "po"
  }
]

export default katakanaDakuten;